https://www.trinityband.co.uk/privacy-cookie-policy/

Privacy & Cookie Policy
1. This privacy policy applies to Trinity Concert Band’s website at www.trinityband.co.uk (the “Website”). We at Trinity Concert Band take your privacy seriously. This policy covers the collection, processing and other use of personal data under the Data Protection Act 1998(“DPA”) and the General Data Protection Regulations (“GDPR”).2. For the purpose of the DPA and GDPR we are the data controller and any enquiry regarding the collection or processing of your data should be addressed to Sandy Godfrey at our address 38 Manor Park Drive, Finchampstead, Wokingham, Berkshire RG40 4XE.3. By using the Website you consent to this policy. We are registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office for this purpose.Information we collect4. We will collect personal data on this Website only if it is directly provided to us by you the user, e.g. your e-mail address, name, home or work address and telephone number, and therefore has been provided by you with your consent. Normally you will only provide suchdetails if you wish to sign up for our free e-newsletter or are buying tickets from us.5. We also use analytical and statistical tools that monitor details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data (but this data will not identify you personally).6. Your payment information (e.g. credit card details) provided when you make a purchase from our website is not received or stored by us. That information is processed securely and privately by the third party payment processors that we use. Trinity Concert Band will nothave access to that information at any time. We may share your personal data with our payment processors, but only for the purpose of completing the relevant payment transaction. Such payment processors are banned from using your personal data, except to provide these necessary payment services to us, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your personal data and payment information.Use of your information7. We may hold and process personal data that you provide to us in accordance with the DPA and GDPR.8. The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you, and to meet our contractual commitments to you. Where you have consented to receive our e-newsletters, from time to time we will provide that for you.Disclosure of your information9. We may disclose your information to regulatory bodies to enable us to comply with the law and to assist fraud protection and minimise credit risk.10. If you have given us consent to use your data for a particular purpose you can revoke or vary that consent at any time. If you do not want us to use your data or want to vary the consent that you have provided you can write to us at the address detailed in clause 2 or email us at dataprotection@trinityband.co.uk at any time.Where we store and transfer your data11. As part of the services offered to you, for example through our Website, the information you provide to us may be transferred to and stored in countries outside of the European Economic Area (EEA) as we use remote website server hosts to provide the website andsome aspects of our service, which may be based outside of the EEA, or use servers based outside of the EEA – this is generally the nature of data stored in “the Cloud”. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for one of our suppliers, e.g. our website server host, or work for us when temporarily outside of the EEA.12. A transfer of your personal data may happen if any of our servers are located in a country outside of the EEA or one of our service providers is located in a country outside of the EEA. If we transfer or store your personal data outside the EEA in this way, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected, as outlined in this privacy policy and in accordance with the DPA and GDPR. If you use our service while you are outside the EEA, your personal data may be transferred outside the EEA in order to provide you with these services.13. We do not use or disclose sensitive personal data, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.14. Otherwise, we will process, disclose or share your personal data only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal requirements or legal process served on us or the website.15. You have the right to opt out of our processing your personal data for marketing purposes by contacting us at dataprotection@trinityband.co.ukSecurity16. The transmission of information via the Internet or email is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of data while you are transmitting it to our site; any such transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your personal data, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.17. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You should choose a password it is not easy for someone to guess.Third party links18. You might find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies, which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.Use of cookies19. This website uses cookies to enhance the user experience. Cookies are small text files that are automatically placed on your computer when you visit websites. The vast majority of websites on the internet use cookies.The purpose of our cookies is to make the website function correctly, to personalise the website to your preferences, and to collect information about your visit which will help us improve the website in the future. We never collect information that could identify you, or pass information to any third parties.You can normally visit this website without identifying who you are or revealing any information about yourself. However, cookies are used to store small amounts of information on your computer, which allows certain information from your web browser to be collected. Cookies are widely used on the internet and do not identify the individual using the computer, just the computer being used. Cookies and other similar technology make it easier for you to log on to and use our website during future visits.By using and browsing this website, you consent to cookies being used. If you do not consent, you must disable cookies in your browser or refrain from using the site.Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.In addition, we use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.Your rights20. The DPA and GDPR give you the right to access information held about you by us. Please write to us or contact us by email if you wish to request confirmation of what personal information we hold relating to you. You can write to us at the address detailed in clause 2, above, or by email to theresamaryj@gmail.com. There is no charge for requesting that we provide you with details of the personal data that we hold. We will provide this information within one month of your requesting the data.21. You have the right to change the permissions that you have given us in relation to how we may use your data. You also have the right to request that we cease using your data or that we delete all personal data records that we hold relating to you. You can exercise these rights at any time by writing to us at the address detailed in clause 2, above, or by email to dataprotection@trinityband.co.uk.Changes to this policy22. We may update these policies to reflect changes to the website and customer feedback. Please regularly review these policies to be informed of how we are protecting your personal data. We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding thisPrivacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us at 38 Manor Park Drive, Finchampstead, Wokingham, Berkshire RG40 4XE or dataprotection@trinityband.co.uk.Version: May 2018This Privacy Policy has been provided by the legal resource www.legalo.co.uk
Trinity Concert Band
Charity No. 1145098
Terms of Use
Privacy & Cookie Policy
Members Area
Website by Blue Room IT
